## **Robert Stevens Pineda Marín**

**Computer Systems Engineer** 

## Profile

Software Developer with at least 6 years of experience in software indstry, designing and building differents types of aplications for the web, backend services and mobile devices. Enhanced skills for problem solving and easy adaptation for continous changes on technologies, programming languages, frameworks and software development tools. Passionate self taught and Reverser Engineering fan.

## Employment History

## **Fullstack Developer at Topitt Inc**

August 2019 - Present

- Design, build and stylish different modules for the web application frontend using the Angular framework.
- Develop some micro services for news scrapping and store them on database using Node.js, MongoDb and AWS Lambda Functions.
- Implementation of Server Side Rendering (SSR) to deal and improve the SEO features for the web application.
- Upgrade and improve built frontend modules to avoid bugs.
- Lazy loading of modules and web resources to improve the performance and loading of the application.

#### Web Development as Freelancer

July 2018 - August 2019

• Build some websites for different customers using PHP frameworks, HTML5 and Javascript (jQuery).

## **Mobile App Developer at Celuweb SAS**

April 2014 - January 2018

- Develop sales force native Android apps for some big companies in Colombia.
- Implement the hybrid mobile apps development to reach the iOS market for the company using Phonegap and Ionic frameworks.

### **Software Developer at Ethereal Game Factory**

December 2011 - February 2014

 Design and Build the Android application for the Secretary of Transit and Municipal Transport of Santiago de Cali to record traffic infringements including an simple image editor to draw the local map of the infringement.

#### **Contact**

+57 310 416 93 87 yo@stevenscol.co stevenscol.co

#### **Skills**

- Javascript
- Node.js
- HTML5 / CSS3
- Responsive Design
- Angular
- React
- Gatsby
- Git
- Java
- Android Development
- Assembler
- Software Reversing
- AWS Cloud
- Linux
- Shell Scripting
- Clean Code
- TDD
- Self Taught

- Fullstack web development of some web applications for different customers using PHP, HTML5 and Javascript (jQuery).
- Build some mini games and landing pages using AdobBuild some mini games and landing pages using Adobe Flash technology and Facebook API for customer's marketing campaigns.

# Education

**Computer Systems Engineer, Universidad del Quindío, Armenia, Quindío** December 2016